export const religionQuestions = { 
    questions: [
                {
                    question: "What does the word expel mean?",
                    answerAlt: ["to imprison","to be kicked out", "to rebel", "to argue with someone"],
                    correctAnswer: "to be kicked out"
                },
                {
                    question: "What was the major reason that started King Philip's War?",
                    answerAlt: ["Ownership of land","To end slavery", "New taxes", "Building forts on Indian lands"],
                    correctAnswer: "Ownership of land"
                },
                {
                    question: "What is the main reason for having a town meeting?",
                    answerAlt: ["Hold religious services","to teach children new laws", "To harvest crops", "To take care of town government"],
                    correctAnswer: "To take care of town government"
                },
                {
                    question: "What is a representative government?",
                    answerAlt: ["The King gives new leaders to colonies","The King sends his laws from England", "People elect their own leaders", "People make their own goods and services"],
                    correctAnswer: "People elect their own leaders"
                },
                {
                    question: "Why did whalers start going on long fishing trips?",
                    answerAlt: ["They wanted to be closer to Europe","They had caught & killed all the whales close to shore", "They were not allowed to hunt so close to shore", "None of the above"],
                    correctAnswer: "They had caught & killed all the whales close to shore"
                },
                {
                    question: "Metacomet was the leader of which Indian tribe?",
                    answerAlt: ["Cherokee","Chumash", "Seminole", "Wampanoag"],
                    correctAnswer: "Wampanoag"
                },
                {
                    question: "In 1700, how many colonists lived in New England?",
                    answerAlt: ["about 50,000","about 90,000", "about 75,000", "about 10,000"],
                    correctAnswer: "about 90,000"
                },
                {
                    question: "The center of town was called the ____________.",
                    answerAlt: ["plaza","meadow", "meeting place", "common"],
                    correctAnswer: "common"
                },
                {
                    question: "What were 2 things made at naval stores?",
                    answerAlt: ["tar and masts","masts and food", "hulls and cannons", "none of the above"],
                    correctAnswer: "tar and masts"
                }
            ]
}



/*
export const religionQuestions = { 
    questions: [
                {
                    question: "Vad händer enligt Buddhismen när man dör?",
                    answerAlt: ["Man kommer till himmelen eller helvetet","Man återföds i ett nytt liv", "Man anses sig inte veta", "Man blir upplyst och når Nirvana"],
                    correctAnswer: "Man återföds i ett nytt liv"
                },
                {
                    question: "Vad händer enligt Judendomen när man dör?",
                    answerAlt: ["Man kommer till himmelen eller helvetet","Man återföds i ett nytt liv", "Man anses sig inte veta", "Man blir upplyst och når Nirvana"],
                    correctAnswer: "Man anses sig inte veta"
                },
                {
                    question: "Vem anses vara Messias enlight Islam?",
                    answerAlt: ["Mohammad","Jesus", "Moses", "Abraham"],
                    correctAnswer: "Jesus"
                },
                {
                    question: "Vad kallas Hinduismens heliga text (textsamling)?",
                    answerAlt: ["Veda","Tanak", "Koranen", "Tripitaka"],
                    correctAnswer: "Veda"
                },
                {
                    question: "Hur många utövare/anhängare har Hinduismen?",
                    answerAlt: ["15 miljoner","900 miljoner", "500 miljoner", "1.8 miljarder"],
                    correctAnswer: "500 miljoner"
                }
            ]
}

*/